<resources>
    <string name="app_name">London</string>
     <!-- Strings used for fragments for navigation -->
    <string name="list_fragment_label">Sport</string>
    <string name="detail_fragment_label">Sport Info</string>

    <string name="app_top_bar">LONDON</string>

    <!-- Category's -->
    <string name="attractions">Attractions</string>
    <string name="attractions_subtitle">Visit the London Eye, explore the Tower of London, and discover treasures at the British Museum.</string>

    <string name="transport">Transport</string>
    <string name="transport_subtitle">Get around London easily with the Underground, iconic red buses, and black cabs.</string>

    <string name="museum">Museum</string>
    <string name="museum_subtitle">Visit world-class museums like the British Museum and the Natural History Museum, many offering free entry.</string>

    <string name="sport_stadium">Sports Stadium</string>
    <string name="sports_stadium_subtitle">Catch thrilling matches at famous stadiums like Wembley, Emirates, and Stamford Bridge.</string>

    <string name="theatre">Theatre</string>
    <string name="theatre_subtitle">Experience unforgettable performances in London\’s West End, the heart of global theatre.</string>

    <string name="parks">Parks</string>
    <string name="parks_subtitle">Relax in London\'s green spaces, from royal parks to hidden gardens.</string>

    <string name="shopping">Shopping</string>
    <string name="shopping_subtitle">Explore London\'s diverse shopping scene, from luxury boutiques to vibrant markets.</string>

    <string name="airport">Airports</string>
    <string name="airport_subtitle">Easily navigate London\'s major airports and discover convenient transport links. Don\'t forget to ask!</string>

    <string name="activities">Activities</string>
    <string name="activities_subtitle">Discover a wide range of activities, from walking tours to unique experiences. Don\'t forget to ask!</string>

    <string name="restaurants">Restaurants</string>
    <string name="restaurants_subtitle">Discover diverse dining options, from traditional pubs to Michelin-starred restaurants. Don\'t forget to ask!</string>

    <!-- Attraction's Recommendations -->
    <string name="warner_bros_studio">Warner Bros. Studio Tour London</string>
    <string name="london_eye">The London Eye</string>
    <string name="hopon_hopoff">Hop-on Hop-off Bus Tour</string>
    <string name="tower_of_london">Tower of London</string>
    <string name="madame_tussauds">Madame Tussauds London</string>
    <string name="buckingham_palace">Buckingham Palace</string>

    <!-- Category 1 for London City / London Attractions -->
    <string name="warner_bros_studio_subtitle"> Have a magical day out with a behind-the-scenes tour of the Harry Potter films at Warner Bros.</string>
    <string name="warner_bros_studio_detail_text">
     Discover the magic behind spellbinding special effects, uncover behind-the-scenes secrets and step onto real-life sets from the Harry Potter film series at Warner Bros. Studio Tour London.
     Watch the magic of the films come to life with original costumes, interactive sets and real props from the Harry Potter film series.
     \n\n
     Explore the iconic Great Hall, wander the cobbles of Diagon Alley and board the Hogwarts Express on Platform 9 \¾ to snap a photo with the iconic luggage trolley.
     This mesmerising studio tour gives you a glimpse into the magical wizarding world that has captivated people from around the world of all ages.
     Explore the Warner Bros. Studio Tour London – The Making of Harry Potter
     Walk in the footsteps of Harry and his friends, and experience magic unfolding before your very eyes.
     \n\n
     Marvel at breathtaking sets, authentic props and original costumes, as you embark on a journey through the marble towers of Gringotts Wizarding Bank, see where students were taught Herbology lessons with Professor Pomona Sprout, and experience the magic of other iconic scenes.
     Spot your favourite props from the films and discover how special and visual effects were used to create the Chamber of Secrets door, invisibility cloak, the flying Quidditch scenes and much more.
     Located within the Studios where all eight films were produced, the Studio Tour showcases the best of British talent, imagination and artistry that went into making the impossible a reality on screen. Relive the magic through the eyes of the filmmakers who brought the Harry Potter film series to life.
     \n\n
     Don’t forget to visit the Studio Tour shops and explore the range of exclusive merchandise, replica wands, collectible items and confectionery to complete the memorable day.
     How to book your Warner Bros. Studio Tour London – The Making of Harry Potter tickets.
     \n\n
     Book Studio Tour tickets with return travel now.
     \n\n
     Ticket options include entry plus travel from London Victoria or Baker Street; or, if you already have tickets for the Studio Tour, there’s the option to purchase return transport only from central London.
     Enhance your Studio Tour experience by visiting around Halloween for the Dark Arts spectacle, summer for Return to Azkaban takeover or book tickets during the Christmas period to celebrate the magical festive season with Hogwarts in the Snow.
     \n\n
     This content has been supplied by Warner Bros. Studio Tour London - The Making of Harry Potter
    </string>

    <string name="london_eye_subtitle">Climb aboard one of the 32 glass capsules of the London Eye for unforgettable views of some of London\'s most famous landmarks.</string>
    <string name="london_eye_detail">
  Experience unparalleled 360-degree views over London on the lastminute.com London Eye - the world’s tallest cantilevered observation wheel at 135m (443 ft) high! Wave hello to some of London\’s most spectacular landmarks, including Big Ben, Buckingham Palace and St Paul’s Cathedral.\n
  Built to celebrate the millennium in 2000, this special engineering achievement has become a symbol of the modern capital and a world-famous icon of architecture.\n
  Enjoy the gradual rotation and views of London life as you soar across the skyline during the daytime or after dark.\n
  \n
  How long does the London Eye take to go around?\n
  A leisurely rotation in one of the 32 high-tech glass pods takes approximately 30 minutes and gives you an ever-changing perspective of London. If you can\’t wait to get up in the sky, you can skip the queues with a fast-track entry ticket.\n
  \n
  How to book London Eye tickets?\n
  Tickets to the London Eye must be pre-booked online with timed entry.\n
  \n
  Do you have to book London Eye tickets in advance?\n
  London Eye tickets must be pre-booked online with timed entry.\n
  \n
  How many pods are on the London Eye?\n
  The London Eye has 32 pods, each representing one of London’s 32 boroughs.\n
  \n
  How tall is the London Eye?\n
  The London Eye is an impressive 135 meters (443 ft) high.\n
  \n
  What can you see from the London Eye?\n
  From the London Eye, you will be able to spot some of the capital’s most iconic landmarks and top attractions including Big Ben, St Paul’s Cathedral, the Houses of Parliament, and Buckingham Palace. On a clear day, you can see up to 40km (25 miles) to Windsor Castle.\n
  \n
  Fun facts about the London Eye!\n
  1. The London Eye travels at a speed of around 0.6 miles per hour, advancing roughly 26 cm every second.\n
  2. There is no 13th capsule as it is believed to be unlucky.\n
  3. The London Eye can hold 800 people per revolution, with a maximum capacity of 25 people per pod.\n
  4. Since 2000, the London Eye has taken more than 70 million people on a journey across London’s skyline, including celebrities such as Kim Kardashian, Mo Farah, Hugh Jackman, and Royal favorites Prince and Princess of Wales Will and Kate.\n
  5. The London Eye weighs 2,100 tonnes – that’s as heavy as 1,272 black cabs.\n
  6. The London Eye is supported by a frame only on one side, making it the largest cantilevered observation wheel in the world.\n
  7. David Marks and Julia Barfield came up with the idea for the London Eye in response to a 1993 competition asking Londoners to design a new landmark celebrating the millennium, and therefore being known as the Millennium Wheel.\n
  8. The lights were changed to LED lighting in 2006, so the London Eye can change colors and light up the sky to mark special occasions such as Coronations, movie premiers, and London community events.\n
  9. On New Year’s Eve, the London Eye is the focal point for the fireworks over the Thames.\n
  \n
  What is the best time to visit the London Eye?\n
  Boarding the London Eye includes some queuing. The quieter times of the day to visit are usually early morning for first entry or later in the day towards last entry.\n
  \n
  During peak periods such as weekends and school holidays, you may experience longer waiting times. You can upgrade your London Eye tickets to fast-track entry when booking online.\n
  \n
  What is the closest tube station to the London Eye?\n
  The London Eye is located on the south bank of the river Thames. London Eye\'s nearest tube station is Waterloo station (Jubilee, Bakerloo, and Northern lines).\n
  Charing Cross (Bakerloo and Northern lines), Westminster (Circle, District, and Jubilee lines), and Embankment (Circle, District, Northern, and Bakerloo lines) are also a short walk away.\n
  \n
  Several bus routes stop near the London Eye: 1, 12, 59, 68, 76, 77, 139, 148, 159, 168, 176, 188, 211, 243, 77 and 381, 507, 521.\n
 </string>

    <string name="hopon_hopoff_subtitle">Make the most of your trip to London with a hop-on hop-off bus tour.</string>
    <string name="hopon_hopoff_detail">
    See London\'s iconic landmarks from the comfort of a hop-on hop-off bus tour. Enjoy unlimited travel around London for 24 or 48 hours, with a free river tour included with your bus ticket.\n
    This convenient service allows you to tick off as much sightseeing as you\'d like across one or two days. Simply board the tour bus at any of the designated stops across the city and hop off at the closest stop to the sight you\'re visiting.\n
    Once you\'re done exploring, get back on the bus and make your way to the next spot!\n

    Your booking also includes access to a free River Thames Boat Ride or a free London walking tour.\n

    What is the bus tour route?\n
    The buses cover four different routes with more than 60 stops, offering plenty of opportunities to see London\'s most famous places. You can hop on and off as many times as you want, giving you the chance to explore areas and attractions in more detail.\n

    Classic Tour (Blue route): All central London sights and London\'s Museum Quarter.\n
    Essential Tour (Red route): Includes Madame Tussauds, Kings Cross, Hyde Park, and Regents Park.\n
    Morning and Evening Drop-Off Service (Yellow and Green routes): Available in the morning and late afternoon, this service operates from popular hotel districts to Central London sights.\n

    Stopping by all major sights, on this hop-on hop-off tour you\'ll have the opportunity to see iconic landmarks including:\n

    Tower of London\n
    Buckingham Palace\n
    Westminster Abbey\n
    Shakespeare\'s Globe\n
    St Paul\'s Cathedral\n
    Tower Bridge\n
    Trafalgar Square\n

    Buses generally operate every 15 to 30 minutes, but this varies by time of year and is subject to change. Be sure to check the most up-to-date timetable on the day of travel.\n

    Look out for the designated Golden Tours Hop on Hop Off/London Tour Bus sign at each stop to ensure you\'re boarding at the right location.\n

    Which languages is the tour in?\n
    Live commentary from an onboard guide, or multilingual audio guides in the following languages are available: English, French, German, Spanish, Italian, Portuguese (Brazilian), Arabic, Japanese, Mandarin, Hindi, and Russian. Free WiFi is also available on the bus.\n

    What is included in the hop-on hop-off tour?\n
    The hop-on hop-off London bus tour includes your bus ticket, audio guides, unlimited travel to over 60 stops across London, and free Wi-Fi on all open-top buses.
     </string>

 <string name="tower_of_london_subtitle">Take a tour with one of the Yeoman Warders around the Tower of London, one of the world\'s most famous buildings.</string>
 <string name="tower_of_london_detail">
 Discover fascinating stories and see iconic sights at London’s famous castle, the Tower of London, where you can explore nearly 1,000 years of its history as a mighty fortress, royal palace and infamous prison.
 Marvel at the 100 objects and 23,000 precious stones that make up the Crown Jewels and enjoy a spectacular new Crown Jewels exhibition that opened in 2023. Learn gruesome tales in the Bloody Tower, meet the Yeoman Warders, walk among plants and flowers in the Moat this summer, and much more at this UNESCO World Heritage site in London.
 \n\n
 What is the Tower of London?
 The Tower of London is one of the world’s most famous fortresses with many tales to uncover within the ancient walls.
 \n\n
 Explore the importance of the Crown Jewels to the British monarchy and the role the Tower plays in protecting these treasures. The gleaming objects include the Coronation Regalia from the Coronation Spoon to St Edward’s Crown. which have been used in the coronation ceremonies of monarchs for centuries, including that of King Charles III and Queen Camilla in 2023.
 Be amazed by the White Tower that was initially built to deter invaders but now houses majestic suits of armour and exciting, hands-on activities for families. The Bloody Tower has an altogether more haunting history – discover murderous tales in this infamous former prison, or learn more about the Tower’s role as a place of torture at Lower Wakefield Tower.
 Delve into the history of the Tower as a royal zoo with sculptures of the Royal Beasts and the Royal Beasts exhibition, and explore the Tower’s Mint exhibition and discover where the majority of the country’s coins were made for more than 500 years.
\n\n
How old is the Tower of London?
William the Conqueror built The Tower of London in 1070. Somewhere between 1075-79, the White Tower was built. However, the Tower received editions in the 13th and 14th centuries.
 \n\n
What was the Tower of London used for?
Find out the story behind the Tower of London. Built as a fortress in the 1070s, it was home to many monarchs for more than 500 years.
\n\n
In 1204, the Tower also hosted the royal menagerie for 600 years, providing housing for many exotic animals.
It might surprise you, but the Tower even served as a Royal Mint from the 13th to 18th century and royals kept precious possessions as well as arms and armour there.
The White Tower, also called Bloody Tower, served as a prison for more than 800 years. Marked by extreme political and religious unrest in the 1500s and 1600s, the Tower was well known for using torture on its inmates. The last execution in the Tower was on 15 August 1941.
  </string>
    <string name="buckingham_palace_subtitle">Enjoy a glimpse into the life of royalty with a visit to this iconic London palace for a limited time each summer.</string>
    <string name="buckingham_palace_detail">
    Buckingham Palace is one of the few working royal palaces remaining in the world today. As one of the most iconic and impressive buildings in the world, it\'s a must visit to experience the best of British history and culture.\n
    Witness the grandeur of the British monarchy and on selected dates during the summer and from November to December and at Easter, visitors can tour the 19 State Rooms, which form the heart of the Palace.\n

    What is there to see?\n
    These magnificent rooms are decorated with some of the greatest treasures from the Royal Collection, including paintings by Rembrandt, Rubens and Canaletto.\n

    The Royal Mews and The King\'s Gallery are part of the Buckingham Palace site, but have their own visitor entrances and so can be visited separately. Both venues are open for most of the year, including when the palace itself is closed.\n

    Try to time your visit to see Changing the Guard, a popular free event which takes place outside Buckingham Palace on certain days from 10.45am and lasts around 45 minutes, with the actual handover taking place at 11am. Be sure to arrive early to secure a spot with a good view.\n
    How can I book tickets for Buckingham Palace?\n
    Tickets for the Buckingham Palace summer tour: summer opening 2025 are currently not available.\n

    Please check back near the time for more information. In the meantime, discover more London royal attractions.\n

    Tickets to visit Buckingham Palace on a guided tour (on selected dates) must be booked in advance via the Royal Collection Trust\'s website.\n

    How long is the Buckingham Palace tour?\n
    It takes between two hours and two hours and 30 minutes to explore Buckingham Palace. Guided tour times may differ.\n

    Where is Buckingham Palace?\n
    Buckingham Palace is located in the City of Westminster in central London.\n
    How to get to Buckingham Palace\n
    The closest Tube stations are Victoria, Green Park and Hyde Park Corner.\n

    Buses 11, 211, C1 and C10 stop near Buckingham Palace.\n

    If you are arriving by coach, Victoria Coach Station is only a 10-minute walk away.\n

    Who lives in Buckingham Palace?\n
    Buckingham Palace serves as the official London residence of His Majesty The King.\n

    The monarch often receives members of the Privy Council, foreign and British Ambassadors and High Commissioners, bishops, senior officers of the Armed Services and the Civil Service.\n

    Many of the royals also hold private apartments here and use the palace as their London home base.\n
    How many rooms are in Buckingham Palace?\n
    Buckingham Palace has 775 rooms in total. This includes:\n

    19 State rooms\n
    52 Royal and guest bedrooms\n
    188 staff bedrooms\n
    92 offices\n
    78 bathrooms\n
    What is the history of Buckingham Palace?\n
    Buckingham Palace is an essential part of England\'s history and culture.\n

    Originally known as Buckingham House, the building at the core of today\'s palace was a large townhouse built for the Duke of Buckingham in 1703, on a site that had been in private ownership for at least 150 years. It was then acquired by King George III in 1761 as a private residence for Queen Charlotte and became known as The Queen\'s House.\n

    During the 19th century, architects John Nash and Edward Blore constructed three wings around a central courtyard.\n

    Buckingham Palace became the official London residence of the British monarch on the accession of Queen Victoria in 1837.\n

    Following major structural additions in the late 19th and early 20th centuries, and the King\'s Gallery built on the site of the destroyed palace chapel during the Second World War, it is now a grand palace with 775 lavishly decorated rooms and the largest private garden in London.\n

    When does Buckingham Palace open to the public?\n
    You can explore the lavishly furnished State Rooms and discover some of the Royal Collection\'s greatest treasures at Buckingham Palace for a limited time each summer.\n

    In 2025, Buckingham Palace will be open to the public from July to September - exact dates to be confirmed.\n

    How many acres is Buckingham Palace?\n
    The Buckingham Palace grounds span more than 39 acres. The garden grounds play a key part in the busy calendar of royal events, official entertaining and celebratory events. The garden boasts wild-plant species, breeding birds and more than 1,000 trees.
</string>

    <string name="attraction_madame_tussauds"> At Madame Tussauds London, you\'ll come face-to-face with some of the world\'s most famous faces.</string>
    <string name="attraction_madame_tussauds_detail">
    Step through the world-famous doors of Madame Tussauds London and immerse yourself into the world of superstars at the ultimate fame experience.\n
    Get closer than ever to your favourite A-listers by coming face to face with more than 150 unique and incredibly realistic figures across three immersive floors.\n

    What\'s inside Madame Tussauds London?\n
    Step through the world-famous doors of Madame Tussauds London and onto the red-carpet where a star-studded experience awaits.\n

    Rub shoulders with Hollywood superstars in the Awards Party, grab the mic and perform with the likes of Drake and Dua Lipa in the Impossible Festival and feel like royalty as you attend a private audience with Their Majesties King Charles III and Queen Camilla in The Royal Palace experience.\n

    All before saving the world with The Avengers in the Marvel Hall of Heroes and wielding the power of the force as you adventure through a galaxy far, far away facing off with legendary Jedi Knights and Sith Lords in Star Wars.\n

    Get closer to the action with immersive experiences throughout Madame Tussauds London. Join the Avengers as they assemble to protect the earth from a new threat in the Marvel Universe 4D experience and truly feel the power of the earth’s mightiest heroes.\n

    Hitch a ride like no other as you hop into an iconic black cab and journey through the capital’s history on the Spirit of London ride. Horror fans rejoice! Enter some of London’s darkest crime scenes of the past 150 years, inside the seriously spine-chilling Chamber of Horrors. At Madame Tussauds London, the fun never stops, with something for the whole family to enjoy.\n

    What is Madame Tussauds London?\n
    Madame Tussauds London is an interactive attraction where you can get up close and personal to some of your favourite icons and A-listers.\n

    There are also four exciting and immersive experiences at Madame Tussauds London, including a unique ride through the capital\'s history on the Spirit of London Ride, entering some of London’s darkest crime scenes of the past 150 years within the Chamber of Horrors and assembling the avengers to face a new threat in the Marvel Universe 4D Experience.\n

    How long does it take to explore Madame Tussauds London?\n
    To fully experience everything that the attraction has to offer, it is recommended you should spend one-and-a-half to two hours during your visit at Madame Tussauds London.\n

    Where is Madame Tussauds London?\n
    Madame Tussauds London is located on Marylebone Road in Marylebone, north-west London.\n

    What is the closest tube station to Madame Tussauds London?\n
    The closest stations are Baker Street Tube Station (Bakerloo, Circle, Jubilee, Metropolitan and Hammersmith &amp; City lines) and Marylebone Station (National Rail).
</string>

    <!--    Category 2 - Museum-->
        <!-- 1. British Museum -->
        <string name="british_museum">The British Museum</string>
        <string name="british_museum_detail">
        Founded in 1753, the British Museum is a treasure trove of human history, art, and culture, showcasing artifacts from around the globe. Its vast collection spans two million years of history. It was the world\'s first public museum of its kind. \n\n
        Highlights include the Rosetta Stone, the Parthenon Sculptures, and Egyptian mummies. The museum\'s diverse exhibits cover everything from ancient civilizations to modern art. There are more than 60 free galleries.  The Great Court is one of the most amazing places. \n\n
        The British Museum is free to enter, but special exhibitions may require a paid ticket. Booking a timed entry ticket in advance is recommended, although some walk-up tickets are available daily. There are shops and restaurants.  \n\n
        Plan to spend at least a few hours exploring this incredible collection.  Don\'t forget to pick up a map at the entrance. Don\'t forget to ask!
    </string>

        <!-- 2. Natural History Museum -->
        <string name="natural_history_museum">The Natural History Museum</string>
        <string name="natural_history_museum_detail">
        The Natural History Museum in South Kensington is an iconic London landmark, with its stunning Victorian architecture. It houses a vast collection of over 80 million specimens. Discover the wonders of the natural world, from dinosaurs to meteorites. \n\n
        Highlights include the awe-inspiring blue whale skeleton, Hope, in Hintze Hall, the world-famous Dinosaurs gallery, and the Earth Galleries. The museum also hosts temporary exhibitions and events.  There are multiple areas to explore, so you can spend hours discovering each of them.\n\n
        Entry to the Natural History Museum is free, but special exhibitions and events may require a ticket. It\'s recommended to book in advance.  The museum is divided into four zones, so you can focus on the areas that interest you most. There are also shops and restaurants. \n\n
        Explore the museum gardens for a peaceful escape, complete with a bronze cast of a Diplodocus. Don\'t forget to check the museum\'s website for events. Don\'t forget to ask!
    </string>

        <!-- 3. Victoria and Albert Museum (V&A) -->
        <string name="victoria_albert_museum">The Victoria and Albert Museum (V&amp;A)</string>
        <string name="victoria_albert_museum_detail">
        The Victoria and Albert Museum, known as the (V&amp;A), is the world\'s leading museum of art, design, and performance. With a collection spanning 5,000 years, it\'s a treasure trove of creativity.  The (V&amp;A) is dedicated to enriching lives through the study of art and design. \n\n
        The museum\'s collections cover everything from ceramics and fashion to furniture and jewelry, representing cultures from around the world. The Cast Courts, with their plaster casts of famous sculptures, are particularly impressive. You will find paintings, sculptures and much more. \n\n
        Entry to the (V&amp;A) is free, but special exhibitions often require paid tickets. Be sure to check the museum\'s website for current exhibitions and events. The museum also has a great gift shop and a cafe. You will find a variety of amazing gardens.\n\n
        Allow plenty of time to wander through the (V&amp;A) diverse collections. Don\'t forget to look up to admire the building\'s intricate details. Don\'t forget to ask!
    </string>

        <!-- 4. Science Museum -->
        <string name="science_museum">The Science Museum</string>
        <string name="science_museum_detail">
        The Science Museum is a fantastic destination for anyone curious about science, technology, engineering, and medicine. It\'s an interactive museum, where visitors can engage with exhibits and learn about the history of science and innovation. The museum have many things to interact with.\n\n
        The museum is full of hands-on exhibits, making it perfect for families and visitors of all ages. There are sections dedicated to space exploration, transportation, and the human body. The museum is divided in sections, such as the Launchpad, who has many interactive exhibits.  \n\n
        Entry to the Science Museum is free, but there may be a charge for special exhibitions or the IMAX cinema. Check the museum\'s website for details on current exhibitions and any special events. You can also book online. \n\n
        Allow ample time to explore the many levels and exhibits.  Don\'t forget to take a photo with the iconic rockets and space crafts. Don\'t forget to ask!
    </string>

        <!-- 5. National Gallery -->
        <string name="national_gallery">The National Gallery</string>
        <string name="national_gallery_detail">
        The National Gallery, located in Trafalgar Square, houses one of the world\'s greatest collections of European paintings, spanning from the 13th to the 19th century.  It\'s a must-visit for art lovers, offering a comprehensive journey through art history. The gallery shows the evolution of painting. \n\n
        The collection includes works by masters such as Van Gogh, Leonardo da Vinci, Michelangelo, and Botticelli.  The paintings are displayed chronologically and by school, making it easy to follow the development of art. The National Gallery is divided into four areas. \n\n
        Entry to the National Gallery is free, but special exhibitions often require a paid ticket.  Be sure to check the gallery\'s website for current exhibition information. There are many tours available. There are also shops and restaurants.  \n\n
        Spend time getting up close to the masterpieces. Don\'t forget to admire the architecture of the building itself. Don\'t forget to ask!
    </string>

        <!-- 6. Tate Modern -->
        <string name="tate_modern">The Tate Modern</string>
        <string name="tate_modern_detail">
        The Tate Modern is Britain\'s national museum of international modern and contemporary art, housed in the former Bankside Power Station. Its iconic Turbine Hall is a must-see. The Tate Modern is a place of experimentation.\n\n
        The collection includes works by artists such as Picasso, Warhol, and Dalí. The museum\'s vast collection is displayed across multiple levels. The museum often hosts temporary exhibitions. The Tate Modern is one of the most interesting places. \n\n
        Entry to the Tate Modern is free, but special exhibitions may require a ticket. Be sure to check the museum\'s website for the latest exhibitions and events. The museum have many guided tours. \n\n
        Take the time to explore the building\'s architecture, as well as the art. Don\'t forget to admire the views of the city from the upper floors. Don\'t forget to ask!
    </string>

        <!-- 7. Churchill War Rooms -->
        <string name="churchill_war_rooms">The Churchill War Rooms</string>
        <string name="churchill_war_rooms_detail">
        The Churchill War Rooms offer a unique glimpse into life during World War II, housed in the underground bunker that served as the British government\'s headquarters during the Blitz. It is where Churchill and his government managed the Second World War.  This is one of the most interesting museum to visit.\n\n
        Explore the Cabinet War Rooms, where Churchill and his government strategized and planned during the war.  Visit the Churchill Museum to learn more about Churchill\'s life and leadership. The museum contains many historical artifacts.\n\n
        Entry to the Churchill War Rooms requires a paid ticket, and it\'s highly recommended to book in advance. This is a very popular attraction, so tickets often sell out. There is a gift shop and a cafe in the museum.\n\n
        Allow at least a couple of hours to fully explore the War Rooms. Don\'t forget to take the audio guide for a more immersive experience. Don\'t forget to ask!
    </string>

<!--    Category 3 - Transport-->
        <!-- 1. The Tube (Underground) -->
        <string name="tube">The London Underground: The Tube</string>
        <string name="tube_detail">
        The London Underground, affectionately known as the \'Tube,\' is the world\'s first underground railway and a vital part of London\'s transport system. With 11 lines and 272 stations, it efficiently connects most of the city and its suburbs. Each line is color-coded and named, making it relatively easy to navigate. The Tube is usually the fastest way to travel across central London, particularly during peak hours when road traffic can be heavy.  \n\n
        Understanding the Tube\'s zones is crucial for planning your journey and purchasing tickets. Zones 1 and 2 cover central London, while the outer zones extend to the suburbs.  Oyster cards and contactless payments are the most convenient ways to pay for your travel.  Make sure you tap in and tap out at the start and end of your journey. \n\n
        During rush hour, the Tube can get incredibly crowded, especially on popular lines. Be prepared to stand or squeeze into packed carriages during peak times.  Also, keep an eye out for service updates, as lines can occasionally be closed for maintenance or experience delays. Despite these challenges, the Tube remains an iconic and incredibly efficient way to explore London.\n\n
        Don\'t forget to download a Tube map app for easy navigation. Remember to mind the gap when entering or exiting the train! It\'s essential to listen for announcements and be aware of your surroundings. Don\'t forget to ask!
    </string>

        <!-- 2. Buses -->
        <string name="buses">London\'s Iconic Red Buses</string>
        <string name="buses_detail">
        London\'s red double-decker buses are an iconic symbol of the city and a fantastic way to see the sights. The bus network is extensive, covering nearly every part of London. There are multiple types of buses and some of them run 24-hours.\n\n
        Buses are generally slower than the Tube, especially during rush hour. However, they provide a more scenic travel experience, allowing you to see more of the city as you go. You can use the same Oyster card or contactless payment method as the Tube, but be sure to only tap in when you board, not when you exit. Buses can take you to various interesting locations, including museums and galleries.\n\n
        Night buses are a lifesaver for those out late. Most night buses are marked with the letter \'N\' before their route number, such as N29. Bus stops are marked with a red sign, and each stop has a list of the routes that pass through it. The bus will stop at every bus station unless the passenger press the stop button. \n\n
        Don\'t forget to download a bus map app to discover all routes! Remember to wave your hand when you see your bus approaching to make sure the driver sees you. Don\'t forget to ask!
    </string>

        <!-- 3. Docklands Light Railway (DLR) -->
        <string name="dlr">Docklands Light Railway (DLR)</string>
        <string name="dlr_detail">
        The Docklands Light Railway (DLR) is an automated light metro system that primarily serves the Docklands area of East London. It connects to the Underground network at several points, providing easy access to Canary Wharf, Greenwich, and London City Airport. The DLR is a great way to travel around the eastern part of the city, especially if you\'re visiting Canary Wharf or Greenwich.\n\n
        One of the unique features of the DLR is that it\'s driverless. This means you can often sit at the front of the train and enjoy the view as it travels through the city. The DLR also operates within the same fare zones as the Underground and buses, and Oyster and contactless payments are accepted.  Many of the stations are above ground, offering great views of the developing Docklands area.\n\n
        The DLR can get quite busy during the work week, as many people commute to Canary Wharf. The trains are frequent, however, so you usually won\'t have to wait long. While it\'s a convenient way to navigate the area, be sure to check service updates, especially on weekends, as there may be planned engineering works.\n\n
        Don\'t forget to plan your journey in advance, especially if you\'re travelling to London City Airport. Remember to tap in and out at the stations to get the correct fare. Don\'t forget to ask!
    </string>

        <!-- 4. Overground -->
        <string name="overground">London Overground</string>
        <string name="overground_detail">
        The London Overground is a suburban railway network that circles much of Greater London, providing connections between areas not directly served by the Underground.  With its distinctive orange roundel, the Overground offers a vital link between the city\'s various districts and suburbs. It is a convenient way to reach locations that are further from the center of London. \n\n
        The Overground connects to the Tube network at numerous stations, making it easy to transfer between the two systems. Oyster cards, contactless payments, and paper tickets are accepted on the Overground, similar to the Tube and buses. Most of the Overground is above ground, giving you an insight into the areas of London outside of the center.\n\n
        The Overground trains are generally less crowded than the Tube, especially outside of peak hours. Be aware that service frequencies can vary depending on the route and time of day.  It\'s always a good idea to check for any planned engineering works before you travel, especially on weekends.\n\n
        Don\'t forget to check the Overground map for useful connections to other transportation options. Remember that this system mainly goes above ground, so you can enjoy the views. Don\'t forget to ask!
    </string>

        <!-- 5. Trams -->
        <string name="trams">London\'s Tram Network</string>
        <string name="trams_detail">
        London\'s tram network, currently known as Tramlink, primarily serves the South London area, particularly around Croydon.  Trams are a smooth, comfortable, and often less crowded alternative to buses, offering a different way to get around in this part of the city. The trams run on dedicated tracks, so they are not affected by road traffic. \n\n
        Tramlink connects to the National Rail network at several stations, making it easy to transfer to other parts of London and beyond. The same Oyster cards and contactless payments used on the Tube and buses are valid on the trams. You only need to tap in when you board the tram, not when you exit. Trams are known for being particularly punctual and for having a smooth ride.\n\n
        The tram network is quite limited compared to the Tube or bus network, focusing primarily on South London. However, it\'s a very useful option if you\'re travelling within the areas it serves. The trams are quite modern and have large windows, so you get a great view of the area. \n\n
        Don\'t forget to check the tram route map if you\'re travelling in South London. Remember to look at the tram destination to ensure you\'re getting on the correct service. Don\'t forget to ask!
    </string>

        <!-- 6. National Rail -->
        <string name="national_rail">National Rail Services</string>
        <string name="national_rail_detail">
        National Rail services are the main intercity train lines that connect London to the rest of the UK.  London has numerous major train stations, each serving different parts of the country.  These stations include King\'s Cross, Paddington, Euston, Victoria, and Waterloo, among others. These stations are usually connected to the Tube and buses.\n\n
        National Rail services are an essential way to reach places outside of London, whether you\'re heading to a coastal town, a historic city, or the countryside.  Trains are generally much faster than buses for long-distance journeys, but ticket prices vary widely depending on the route and the time of travel. It\'s important to plan your journey ahead.\n\n
        You can often get discounted fares if you book your tickets in advance, especially for long-distance travel.  Make sure to check the departure platform and any potential delays before you travel. Train stations can be very busy, especially during rush hour, so give yourself plenty of time to navigate through them. There are usually many shops and restaurants in the train stations.\n\n
        Don\'t forget to check your train schedule and departure platform carefully. Remember to be aware of your belongings at all times, especially in busy stations. Don\'t forget to ask!
    </string>

        <!-- 7. River Bus (Thames Clippers) -->
        <string name="river_bus">River Bus (Thames Clippers)</string>
        <string name="river_bus_detail">
        The River Bus, also known as Thames Clippers, is a unique way to travel around London and offers a different perspective of the city from the River Thames.  The River Bus operates a network of piers between Putney and Wool
        </string>







<!--    <string name="attraction_science_museum">The Science Museum is home to award-winning exhibitions, iconic objects and stories of incredible scientific achievement.</string>-->
<!--    <string name="attraction_science_museum_detail">-->
<!--    The Science Museum is home to award-winning exhibitions, iconic objects and stories of incredible scientific achievement.\n-->
<!--    The Museum’s interactive galleries bring science to life, where you can see lightning strike before your eyes, play with forces on giant slides or travel through space under a canopy of stars.\n-->

<!--    What kind of exhibitions can you see at the Science Museum?\n-->
<!--    There are four floors of educational and interactive exhibits, including the Soyuz TMA-19M descent module – the spacecraft that took astronaut Tim Peake back to Earth from the International Space Station, and a real piece of the Moon.\n-->

<!--    What can I explore at the Science Museum?\n-->
<!--    You can explore the free galleries of the Science Museum, by walking beneath real rockets in Exploring Space; visiting the largest medical galleries in the world in Medicine: The Wellcome Galleries; diving into the role of mathematics in our lives in Mathematics: The Winton Gallery; or discovering some of the most iconic items that have shaped our society in Making the Modern World, from the Apollo 10 capsule module to Crick and Watson’s DNA model.\n-->
<!--    Budding scientists can be amazed by live science shows and enjoy demonstrations led by a talented team of Explainers in Wonderlab, while teenagers can discover an interactive world of STEM careers in Technicians: The David Sainsbury Gallery.\n-->
<!--    Plus, you can immerse yourself in the hands-on gaming experience Power Up, watch a 3D documentary on a screen taller than four double-decker buses in IMAX: The Ronson Theatre, visit the museum after-hours during adults-only Lates, or spend the night at the museum for Astronights, enchanting children sleepovers.\n-->

<!--    How long does the Science Museum take?\n-->
<!--    You are welcome to explore the museum for as long as you would like, but an average visit takes around two hours.\n-->

<!--    Is it free to enter the Science Museum London?\n-->
<!--    Entry to the museum is free, but pre-booking is required.\n-->
<!--    Charges apply for Wonderlab, Power Up, movies at IMAX: The Ronson Theatre and some special exhibitions and events. Family discounts and concessions are also available.\n-->

<!--    Do I need to book tickets to the Science Museum?\n-->
<!--    All visitors are required to pre-book a free ticket to the Science Museum for their visit. You can book these tickets online. If you’re unable to book via the website, you can do so by calling the Science Museum Contact Centre on 033 0058 0058 or emailing them at info@ScienceMuseumGroup.ac.uk.\n-->

<!--    When is the Science Museum open?\n-->
<!--    The Science Museum is open daily from 10am to 6pm. Last entry is 5.15pm. Galleries start to close 30 minutes before the museum closes.\n-->
<!--    Over the Christmas period, the museum is closed from December 24 to December 26.\n-->

<!--    Where is the Science Museum in London?\n-->
<!--    The Science Museum is located on Exhibition Road, in South Kensington, in London, and only a couple minutes’ walk from its neighbouring museums, the Victoria and Albert Museum and the National History Museum.\n-->

<!--    How to get to the Science Museum in London\n-->
<!--    You can get to the Science Museum by Tube, bus, bike and car.\n-->
<!--    Tube – The South Kensington station, running on the District, Circle and Piccadilly lines, is approximately a five-minute walk from the Museum. Gloucester Road Station running on the District, Circle and Piccadilly lines, is within 14 minutes’ walk from the Museum. Please note that there is very limited step-free access across these stations. The nearest step free station is Earl’s Court station, which is within a 25-minute walk from the museum.\n-->
<!--    Buses – The South Kensington Underground Station serving bus routes 14, 49, 70, 74, 345, 360, 414, 430 and C1, which are all close to the Science Museum.\n-->
<!--    Bus routes 9, 10, 52, 452 and 70 stop outside the Royal Albert Hall on Kensington Gore.\n-->
<!--    Bike – Santander Cycle docking stations are available on Exhibition Road, just outside the V&amp;A South Kensington and the National History Museum (next door to the Science Museum), and on Thurloe Place near South Kensington Tube station.\n-->
<!--    Car and parking – There is pay and display car parking near the Museum on Prince Consort Road and Queen’s Gate. Please note that visitor parking is not available on Exhibition Road and local parking sites are also very limited. There are a few accessible parking spaces available on Exhibition Road. Blue badge holders can park in these spaces for four hours between 8.30am and 6.30pm. Royal Borough of Kensington and Chelsea have more information about parking near the museum.\n-->

<!--    Can I get food at the Science Museum?\n-->
<!--    There are several cafés and picnic areas located in the Science Museum. You can pre-order your lunch and collect your order from the designated collection point in the Energy Café during your visit.\n-->
<!--    You are welcome to bring your own food and drink, which you can enjoy in one of the dedicated picnic areas. These can be found on level -1 and level 3.\n-->
<!--    On arrival, please speak to a member of staff to find out which cafés are open during your visit.\n-->

<!--    Is the Science Museum suitable for kids?\n-->
<!--    The Science Museum has interactive, multi-sensory areas for children to discover science through play. Teenagers can enjoy hands on exhibits while events aimed at kids of all ages are held regularly at the Museum.\n-->

<!--    This content has been supplied by Science Museum-->
<!--</string>-->
<!--    <string name="attraction_london_transport_museum">Delve into the history of planet Earth in the Natural History Museum’s galleries</string>-->
<!--    <string name="attraction_london_transport_museum_detail">-->
<!--    Discover the story of London\'s transport past and present at the London Transport Museum.\n-->
<!--    Explore the showcase of transport icons and their groundbreaking design, from the iconic red London bus, first ever Tube map design and the world\'s first underground steam train.\n-->
<!--    See how London’s growth, culture and society have been intertwined with its transport system, from 1800 to the present day.\n-->

<!--    What is there to see at the London Transport Museum?\n-->
<!--    Follow the evolution of iconic vehicles, spot the world\'s first underground steam train and examine the padded cell, a train carriage dating back to the 1890s.\n-->
<!--    Design lovers can marvel at the Design for Travel gallery, featuring pioneering advertising posters and artworks. Spot Harry Beck\'s original design for his groundbreaking London Underground map and chart the development of the world-famous roundel transport logo.\n-->
<!--    Get hands-on at interactive galleries, where you can step aboard real buses and trains and have a go on a Tube driving simulator.\n-->
<!--    If you’re keen to see more of the collection, visit the London Transport Museum Depot in Acton on one of its open days.\n-->

<!--    How can I book tickets?\n-->
<!--    Tickets must be booked in advance – book London Transport Museum tickets now.\n-->
<!--    Make sure to leave enough time to browse the London Transport Museum shop and refuel in the Canteen cafe, both of which are free to enter without a ticket.\n-->
<!--    Full of London transport-themed gifts and souvenirs, the shop is a great place to pick up something unique. Find vintage Underground posters, furnishings inspired by classic designs and Transport for London branded items.\n-->
<!--    The Canteen overlooks Covent Garden Piazza and serves Insta-worthy coffees, sandwiches, soups and salads.\n-->

<!--    How long does it take to walk around the museum?\n-->
<!--    With so many fascinating exhibits, you can easily spend at least two hours walking around the London Transport Museum.\n-->

<!--    Where is the London Transport Museum?\n-->
<!--    The London Transport Museum is in Covent Garden Piazza, directly opposite the main Covent Garden Market building.\n-->

<!--    How to get to the London Transport Museum\n-->
<!--    The London Transport Museum is in Covent Garden.\n-->

<!--    How to get there:\n-->
<!--    Underground – The nearest tube station is Covent Garden (Piccadilly line). Leicester Square (Piccadilly and Northern lines), Holborn (Central and Piccadilly lines), Charing Cross (Bakerloo and Northern lines) and Embankment (Bakerloo, Northern and Circle and District lines) are all within a 10 minute walk.\n-->
<!--    Bus – The closest bus stops are Savoy Street, Southampton Street/Covent Garden, Lancaster Place and Aldwych.\n-->
<!--    Cycling – Hire a Santander Cycles bike and head to the London Transport Museum. The nearest Santander Cycles docking station is Tavistock Street.\n-->
<!--    This content has been supplied by London Transport Museum-->
<!--</string>-->
<!--    <string name="attraction_british_library">The British Library is the UK\'s national library.</string>-->
<!--    <string name="attraction_british_library_detail">-->
<!--    The British Library is the UK\'s national library. It\'s home to over 170 million collection items covering every age of written civilisation, from Magna Carta, to Jane Austen\'s notebooks, to lyrics handwritten by the Beatles. The Library is currently closed, but we\'re always open online with digital events, collections and exhibitions that you can explore wherever you are.\n-->
<!--    Every year the British Library hosts a range of free and ticketed exhibitions. All year round, you can visit the Treasures Gallery - \'the holy grail for history buffs\' (Time Out). Discover iconic items such as Leonardo da Vinci\'s manuscripts and letters by Ada Lovelace. Or visit the Sound Gallery, a free immersive experience where you can listen to some of the 7 million sounds in the Library\'s collection, handpicked by curators.\n-->
<!--    The Library also hosts a lively, ever-changing programme of talks, courses, Lates and family events inspired by both its exhibitions and diverse collection. Top off your visit by stopping for a bite to eat in one of the cafes or the restaurant. And pick up the perfect keepsake at the Shop, stocked with gifts for the curious and literary minded.\n-->
<!--    This content has been supplied by British Library-->
<!--</string>-->

<!--     &lt;!&ndash; Category 3 for London City / Transport for London &ndash;&gt;-->
<!--    <string name="attraction_">The London Underground rail network, also called "the Tube"</string>-->
<!--    <string name="attraction_detail">-->
<!--    The London Underground rail network, also called "the Tube," is a great way to travel to, from and around central London.\n-->
<!--    Greater London is served by 11 Tube lines, along with the Docklands Light Railway (DLR), the London Overground, the Elizabeth line and National Rail services.\n-->
<!--    London Underground trains generally run between 5am and midnight Monday to Saturday. Operating hours are slightly reduced on Sunday. Night Tube trains run on some lines throughout the night on Fridays and Saturdays.\n-->
<!--    For more detailed travel information on which stations to use and suggestions for the best route to reach your destination, use Transport for London\'s Journey Planner.\n-->

<!--    What are the London Underground zones?\n-->
<!--    London\'s public transport network is divided into nine travel zones. Zone 1 is in central London and zones 6 to 9 are on the outskirts of the city.\n-->

<!--    The Elizabeth line\n-->
<!--    Hop onboard London’s Elizabeth line, which connects London Heathrow Airport and Reading to Shenfield and Abbey Wood via major central London Underground and rail stations, including Paddington, Liverpool Street and Canary Wharf stations.\n-->

<!--    What are the London Tube prices?\n-->
<!--    Buy a Visitor Oyster card*, Oyster card, Travelcard or use a contactless payment card to get the best value. A Visitor Oyster card is cheaper to purchase than a regular Oyster card and can be sent to your home address before you arrive in London.\n-->
<!--    If your contactless payment card was issued outside the UK, check with your bank before you travel to see whether you\'ll incur additional transaction fees or charges.\n-->
<!--    For more details about London Tube prices, see the Transport for London website.\n-->
<!--    Various discounts are available for children, students and older travellers on the London Underground.\n-->
<!--    Check out this guide to cheap travel for more money-saving tips when travelling in London.\n-->
<!--    Find out more information about London Oyster cards with these frequently asked questions.\n-->
<!--    If you plan on travelling around London to do some sightseeing and visit some of London\'s best attractions, a London Pass* could save you money.\n-->
<!--</string>-->
<!--    <string name="attraction_london_bus">London\'s iconic double-decker buses are a convenient and cheap way to travel around the city</string>-->
<!--    <string name="attraction_london_bus_detail">-->
<!--    London\'s iconic double-decker buses are a convenient and cheap way to travel around the city, with plenty of sightseeing opportunities along the way.\n-->
<!--    London’s bus route network covers the entire city with a 24-hour service. Read on to find out all you need to know about bus travel in London.\n-->

<!--    Pay your fare on cash-free London buses\n-->
<!--    London buses are card only, so you cannot buy a ticket with cash.\n-->
<!--    Use a Visitor Oyster card*, an Oyster card, a Travelcard or a contactless payment card to pay your fare.\n-->
<!--    Unlike the Tube zone fare system, a single London bus journey costs £1.75 no matter how far you go. You can even take multiple buses within one hour at no extra charge thanks to the Hopper fare. No matter how many buses or trams you take in a day, it will never cost you more than £5.25 total – just make sure you use the same payment card for every journey.\n-->
<!--    For contactless payment cards issued outside the UK, check with your bank to find out whether transaction fees or other charges apply.\n-->
<!--    Paying your London bus fare is easy. Simply touch your Oyster card or contactless payment card on the yellow card reader as you board the bus or show the driver your paper Travelcard. To avoid card clash, make sure to only touch one card on the yellow reader and keep your other cards separate.\n-->
<!--    If you don’t have enough credit on your Visitor Oyster card or Oyster card, you will be able to make one more journey on a bus before needing to top up.\n-->
<!--    For more information about London bus fares, see the Transport for London website.\n-->
<!--    Still not sure which travel ticket you need to buy? Unclear on how to use your Visitor Oyster card? Read our Oyster FAQs section for the answer to these and other Oyster-related questions.\n-->
<!--</string>-->

     <!-- Category 4 for London City / Theatre -->
<!--    <string name="attraction_natural_history_museum">Delve into the history of planet Earth in the Natural History Museum’s galleries</string>-->
<!--    <string name="attraction_warnerbros_studio_detail">-->
<!--      Have a magical day out with a behind-the-scenes tour of the Harry Potter films at Warner Bros.-->
<!--      Studio Tour London The Making of Harry Potter. See first-hand the sets, costumes and props used in all the Harry Potter films, and step inside some of the films locations, including the Great Hall, Dumbledore\'s office and Hagrid\'s hut.-->
<!--      It\'s the ultimate Harry Potter experience!-->
<!--    </string>-->

<!--     &lt;!&ndash; Category 5 for London City / Sports Venue &ndash;&gt;-->
<!--    <string name="attraction_natural_history_museum">Delve into the history of planet Earth in the Natural History Museum’s galleries</string>-->
<!--    <string name="attraction_warnerbros_studio_detail">-->
<!--      Have a magical day out with a behind-the-scenes tour of the Harry Potter films at Warner Bros.-->
<!--      Studio Tour London The Making of Harry Potter. See first-hand the sets, costumes and props used in all the Harry Potter films, and step inside some of the films locations, including the Great Hall, Dumbledore\'s office and Hagrid\'s hut.-->
<!--      It\'s the ultimate Harry Potter experience!-->
<!--    </string>-->
<!--     <string name="back_button">Back</string>-->
</resources>
