<resources>
    <string name="app_name">London</string>
     <!-- Strings used for fragments for navigation -->
    <string name="list_fragment_label">Sport</string>
    <string name="detail_fragment_label">Sport Info</string>

    <string name="app_top_bar">LONDON</string>

    <!-- Category's -->
    <string name="attractions">Attractions</string>
    <string name="attractions_subtitle">Visit the London Eye, explore the Tower of London, and discover treasures at the British Museum.</string>

    <string name="transport">Transport</string>
    <string name="transport_subtitle">Get around London easily with the Underground, iconic red buses, and black cabs.</string>

    <string name="museum">Museum</string>
    <string name="museum_subtitle">Visit world-class museums like the British Museum and the Natural History Museum, many offering free entry.</string>

    <string name="sport_stadium">Sports Stadium</string>
    <string name="sports_stadium_subtitle">Catch thrilling matches at famous stadiums like Wembley, Emirates, and Stamford Bridge.</string>

    <string name="theatre">Theatre</string>
    <string name="theatre_subtitle">Experience unforgettable performances in London\’s West End, the heart of global theatre.</string>

    <string name="parks">Parks</string>
    <string name="parks_subtitle">Relax in London\'s green spaces, from royal parks to hidden gardens.</string>

    <string name="shopping">Shopping</string>
    <string name="shopping_subtitle">Explore London\'s diverse shopping scene, from luxury boutiques to vibrant markets.</string>

    <string name="airport">Airports</string>
    <string name="airport_subtitle">Easily navigate London\'s major airports and discover convenient transport links. Don\'t forget to ask!</string>

    <string name="activities">Activities</string>
    <string name="activities_subtitle">Discover a wide range of activities, from walking tours to unique experiences. Don\'t forget to ask!</string>

    <string name="restaurants">Restaurants</string>
    <string name="restaurants_subtitle">Discover diverse dining options, from traditional pubs to Michelin-starred restaurants. Don\'t forget to ask!</string>


    <!-- 1. Warner Bros. Studio Tour London -->
    <string name="warner_bros_studio">Warner Bros. Studio Tour London</string>
    <string name="warner_bros_studio_subtitle">The Making of Harry Potter</string>
    <string name="warner_bros_studio_detail">
        Step into the magical world of Harry Potter at Warner Bros. Studio Tour London – The Making of Harry Potter. This incredible attraction invites you to explore the authentic sets, discover behind-the-scenes secrets, and marvel at the intricate props and costumes from the beloved film series.  Walk through iconic locations like the Great Hall, Diagon Alley, and the Forbidden Forest. This is a must-visit place for Harry Potter fans.\n\n
        You\'ll have the chance to see how special effects and animatronics were brought to life in the films, and you can even try your hand at riding a broomstick!  The studio tour is a journey through the creativity and craftsmanship that went into making the magical world of Harry Potter a reality. There are also many shops and restaurants.\n\n
        Tickets for the Warner Bros. Studio Tour must be booked in advance, as this is a very popular attraction.  The studio is located just outside of London, but there are easy transportation options to get there.  Allow yourself at least 3 to 4 hours to fully enjoy the tour and all it has to offer. This is one of the best activities to do.\n\n
        Don\'t forget to try some Butterbeer, a delicious treat from the wizarding world. Remember to take your camera to capture all the magic. Don\'t forget to ask!
    </string>

    <!-- 2. The London Eye -->
    <string name="london_eye">The London Eye</string>
    <string name="london_eye_subtitle">Panoramic Views of London</string>
    <string name="london_eye_detail">
        The London Eye is an iconic observation wheel located on the South Bank of the River Thames.  It offers breathtaking 360-degree views of London\'s skyline, providing a unique perspective on the city\'s famous landmarks. The London Eye is one of the most visited tourist place. \n\n
        As you slowly rotate in one of the Eye\'s capsules, you\'ll be able to spot landmarks such as the Houses of Parliament, Big Ben, Buckingham Palace, and St. Paul\'s Cathedral. On a clear day, you can see up to 40 kilometers away. There are also many shops and restaurants near the London Eye.\n\n
        Tickets for the London Eye can be booked in advance online, which is highly recommended to avoid long queues. The ride in each capsule lasts about 30 minutes. You can also get fast-track tickets for shorter queue times. There are usually restaurants around.\n\n
        Don\'t forget to check the weather forecast before your visit to make sure you have clear views. Remember to take photos from the top. Don\'t forget to ask!
    </string>

    <!-- 3. Hop-On Hop-Off Bus Tour -->
    <string name="hopon_hopoff">Hop-On Hop-Off Bus Tour</string>
    <string name="hopon_hopoff_subtitle">Explore London at Your Own Pace</string>
    <string name="hopon_hopoff_detail">
        A Hop-On Hop-Off bus tour is a fantastic way to explore London\'s major attractions at your own pace.  These open-top, double-decker buses stop at key locations throughout the city, allowing you to get off and explore whenever and wherever you want. There are multiple companies that offers this service. \n\n
        With a Hop-On Hop-Off ticket, you can hop on and off the bus as many times as you like within the ticket\'s validity period.  Audio commentary is provided on board, giving you interesting information about the landmarks you pass. There are multiple routes available. \n\n
        A Hop-On Hop-Off bus tour is a great way to get an overview of the city and decide which attractions you want to explore in more detail. They go past most of the iconic locations.  You can purchase tickets online or from kiosks near the bus stops. This is one of the most popular attractions.\n\n
        Don\'t forget to plan which stops you want to visit before you start your tour. Remember to bring sunscreen and water on sunny days. Don\'t forget to ask!
    </string>

    <!-- 4. Tower of London -->
    <string name="tower_of_london">The Tower of London</string>
    <string name="tower_of_london_subtitle">History and Crown Jewels</string>
    <string name="tower_of_london_detail">
        The Tower of London is one of London\'s most iconic landmarks, steeped in over 900 years of history.  This historic castle has served as a royal palace, prison, armoury, and even a zoo! It is one of the most popular tourist attractions in the United Kingdom. \n\n
        Highlights of a visit to the Tower include seeing the Crown Jewels, meeting the Yeoman Warders (Beefeaters), and exploring the White Tower.  You\'ll learn about the Tower\'s history as a place of both royalty and imprisonment. You will discover the legend of the ravens and why they must stay in the Tower.\n\n
        Tickets for the Tower of London can be purchased online or at the entrance, but it\'s often cheaper and quicker to book in advance. There are usually a lot of visitors.  Allow at least 3 hours to explore the Tower fully. The Tower is huge and it has many stories. \n\n
        Don\'t forget to take a guided tour with a Yeoman Warder to hear fascinating stories about the Tower. Remember to bring comfortable shoes, as you\'ll be doing a lot of walking. Don\'t forget to ask!
    </string>

    <!-- 5. Buckingham Palace -->
    <string name="buckingham_palace">Buckingham Palace</string>
    <string name="buckingham_palace_subtitle">Royal Residence</string>
    <string name="buckingham_palace_detail">
        Buckingham Palace is the official London residence of the British monarch and a symbol of the UK.  It\'s a must-see attraction for anyone visiting London, especially for those interested in royal history and pageantry. It is located in Westminster.\n\n
        The most famous event at Buckingham Palace is the Changing of the Guard ceremony, which takes place daily during the summer months and on alternate days in winter.  During the summer, you can also tour the State Rooms within the Palace. It is a unique experience. \n\n
        Tickets to tour the State Rooms need to be booked in advance, as they are only open for a limited time each year.  The Royal Mews and the Queen\'s Gallery are other parts of Buckingham Palace that are open to the public. There are also shops and restaurants around.\n\n
        Don\'t forget to check the schedule for the Changing of the Guard ceremony. Remember to take photos of the palace and the guards. Don\'t forget to ask!
    </string>

    <!-- 6. St. Paul's Cathedral -->
    <string name="st_pauls_cathedral">St. Paul\'s Cathedral</string>
    <string name="st_pauls_cathedral_subtitle">Wren\'s Masterpiece</string>
    <string name="st_pauls_cathedral_detail">
        St. Paul\'s Cathedral is an iconic part of the London skyline and a masterpiece designed by Sir Christopher Wren. This magnificent cathedral has been a symbol of resilience and hope for over 300 years, surviving the Great Fire of London and the Blitz. It is one of the most famous and beautiful churches.\n\n
        Visitors can climb to the top of the Dome for breathtaking views of London, visit the Whispering Gallery, and explore the vast crypt. The cathedral\'s architecture and stunning mosaics are a sight to behold. You will find shops and restaurants around the cathedral.\n\n
        Tickets to St. Paul\'s Cathedral can be purchased online or at the door, but booking online in advance is often recommended, especially during peak tourist seasons. Allow at least 2 to 3 hours to fully explore the cathedral and its grounds. \n\n
        Don\'t forget to check the cathedral\'s website for any special services or events. Remember to take your time admiring the intricate details of the architecture. Don\'t forget to ask!
    </string>

    <!-- 7. Madame Tussauds London -->
    <string name="madame_tussauds">Madame Tussauds London</string>
    <string name="madame_tussauds_subtitle">Meet the Stars</string>
    <string name="madame_tussauds_detail">
        Madame Tussauds London is a world-famous wax museum, where you can come face-to-face with incredibly lifelike wax figures of your favorite celebrities, historical icons, and sports stars. It\'s a unique opportunity to get up close and personal with some of the most famous people in the world.\n\n
        Explore the various themed areas, including the Royal Family, Marvel Super Heroes, Star Wars, and the World Leaders zone. You can take photos with your favorite figures, and learn about the history of Madame Tussauds. It is one of the most fun places to go. \n\n
        Tickets for Madame Tussauds are best booked online in advance, especially during peak tourist seasons. Allow at least 2 to 3 hours to explore the various exhibits. There are usually shops and restaurants inside. \n\n
        Don\'t forget to check the website for any special events or new figure launches. Remember to charge your phone or camera, as you will take a lot of photos. Don\'t forget to ask!
    </string>

    <!-- 8. Borough Market -->
    <string name="borough_market">Borough Market</string>
    <string name="borough_market_subtitle">London\'s Foodie Haven</string>
    <string name="borough_market_detail">
        Borough Market is one of London\'s oldest and most renowned food markets, offering an incredible array of fresh produce, artisanal goods, and delicious street food from around the world. It\'s a paradise for food lovers, with something to tempt every palate. It is located close to London Bridge.\n\n
        Wander through the stalls, sample cheeses, meats, and baked goods, or grab a bite from one of the many street food vendors. The atmosphere is vibrant and bustling, making it a great place to soak up the local culture. There are multiple restaurants around the area. \n\n
        Borough Market is open most days, but it\'s particularly lively on weekends. Be prepared for large crowds, especially during peak times. Don\'t forget to bring an appetite. You will have a great experience. \n\n
        Don\'t forget to try some of the local specialties. Remember to explore all areas of the market, as there\'s something new to discover around every corner. Don\'t forget to ask!
    </string>

    <!-- 9. Tower Bridge -->
    <string name="tower_bridge">Tower Bridge</string>
    <string name="tower_bridge_subtitle">Iconic Victorian Engineering</string>
    <string name="tower_bridge_detail">
        Tower Bridge is one of London\'s most iconic landmarks, a masterpiece of Victorian engineering that spans the River Thames. More than just a bridge, it\'s a unique attraction that offers stunning views and a fascinating history. It is one of the most famous places.\n\n
        Walk across the high-level walkways, with their glass floors, and enjoy panoramic views of London. Visit the Victorian Engine Rooms to see how the bridge was originally operated. You can learn about the construction of the bridge and its role in London\'s history. You will also discover the most beautiful views.\n\n
        Tickets can be purchased online or at the entrance, but booking in advance is recommended. Allow at least 1 to 2 hours to fully explore Tower Bridge. There are usually shops and restaurants around the area.\n\n
        Don\'t forget to check the lift schedule to see the bridge open. Remember to take plenty of photos from the walkways and by the river. Don\'t forget to ask!
    </string>

    <!-- 10. Sky Garden -->
    <string name="sky_garden">Sky Garden</string>
    <string name="sky_garden_subtitle">London\'s Highest Public Garden</string>
    <string name="sky_garden_detail">
        The Sky Garden is a unique public space located at the top of 20 Fenchurch Street, also known as the \'Walkie Talkie\' building. It offers breathtaking 360-degree views of London\'s skyline, along with beautifully landscaped gardens, observation decks, and restaurants. It is a unique way to see the city.\n\n
        Explore the various gardens, take in the spectacular views, or enjoy a meal or a drink at one of the restaurants or bars. The Sky Garden is free to enter, but you must book your tickets in advance. There are many great options to have lunch and dinner.\n\n
        Tickets are released several weeks in advance, so plan ahead. It is recommended to visit during the day and night for a different experience. This is one of the best views in the city.\n\n
        Don\'t forget to bring your camera, as the views are truly incredible. Remember to check their website for any special events or opening times. Don\'t forget to ask!
    </string>

    <!-- 11. Camden Town -->
    <string name="camden_town">Camden Town</string>
    <string name="camden_town_subtitle">Alternative and Vibrant Hub</string>
    <string name="camden_town_detail">
        Camden Town is a unique and vibrant district in North London, famous for its alternative culture, markets, and music scene.  It\'s a place where you can find everything from vintage clothing and handmade crafts to delicious street food and live music venues. Camden is one of the most famous places.\n\n
        Wander through the many markets, browse the eclectic shops, or explore the Regent\'s Canal area.  Camden is also home to a wide range of pubs, bars, and clubs, making it a popular spot for nightlife. There are usually events in the area.\n\n
        Camden is easily accessible by public transport, with its own Underground station. Be prepared for large crowds, especially on weekends.  You can spend a whole day exploring Camden, as there is so much to see and do.\n\n
        Don\'t forget to try some of the diverse street food options. Remember to explore the canal area for a more peaceful escape from the crowds. Don\'t forget to ask!
    </string>

    <!--    Category 2 - Museum-->
        <!-- 1. British Museum -->
        <string name="british_museum">The British Museum</string>
        <string name="british_museum_detail">
        Founded in 1753, the British Museum is a treasure trove of human history, art, and culture, showcasing artifacts from around the globe. Its vast collection spans two million years of history. It was the world\'s first public museum of its kind. \n\n
        Highlights include the Rosetta Stone, the Parthenon Sculptures, and Egyptian mummies. The museum\'s diverse exhibits cover everything from ancient civilizations to modern art. There are more than 60 free galleries.  The Great Court is one of the most amazing places. \n\n
        The British Museum is free to enter, but special exhibitions may require a paid ticket. Booking a timed entry ticket in advance is recommended, although some walk-up tickets are available daily. There are shops and restaurants.  \n\n
        Plan to spend at least a few hours exploring this incredible collection.  Don\'t forget to pick up a map at the entrance. Don\'t forget to ask!
    </string>

        <!-- 2. Natural History Museum -->
        <string name="natural_history_museum">The Natural History Museum</string>
        <string name="natural_history_museum_detail">
        The Natural History Museum in South Kensington is an iconic London landmark, with its stunning Victorian architecture. It houses a vast collection of over 80 million specimens. Discover the wonders of the natural world, from dinosaurs to meteorites. \n\n
        Highlights include the awe-inspiring blue whale skeleton, Hope, in Hintze Hall, the world-famous Dinosaurs gallery, and the Earth Galleries. The museum also hosts temporary exhibitions and events.  There are multiple areas to explore, so you can spend hours discovering each of them.\n\n
        Entry to the Natural History Museum is free, but special exhibitions and events may require a ticket. It\'s recommended to book in advance.  The museum is divided into four zones, so you can focus on the areas that interest you most. There are also shops and restaurants. \n\n
        Explore the museum gardens for a peaceful escape, complete with a bronze cast of a Diplodocus. Don\'t forget to check the museum\'s website for events. Don\'t forget to ask!
    </string>

        <!-- 3. Victoria and Albert Museum (V&A) -->
        <string name="victoria_albert_museum">The Victoria and Albert Museum (V&amp;A)</string>
        <string name="victoria_albert_museum_detail">
        The Victoria and Albert Museum, known as the (V&amp;A), is the world\'s leading museum of art, design, and performance. With a collection spanning 5,000 years, it\'s a treasure trove of creativity.  The (V&amp;A) is dedicated to enriching lives through the study of art and design. \n\n
        The museum\'s collections cover everything from ceramics and fashion to furniture and jewelry, representing cultures from around the world. The Cast Courts, with their plaster casts of famous sculptures, are particularly impressive. You will find paintings, sculptures and much more. \n\n
        Entry to the (V&amp;A) is free, but special exhibitions often require paid tickets. Be sure to check the museum\'s website for current exhibitions and events. The museum also has a great gift shop and a cafe. You will find a variety of amazing gardens.\n\n
        Allow plenty of time to wander through the (V&amp;A) diverse collections. Don\'t forget to look up to admire the building\'s intricate details. Don\'t forget to ask!
    </string>

        <!-- 4. Science Museum -->
        <string name="science_museum">The Science Museum</string>
        <string name="science_museum_detail">
        The Science Museum is a fantastic destination for anyone curious about science, technology, engineering, and medicine. It\'s an interactive museum, where visitors can engage with exhibits and learn about the history of science and innovation. The museum have many things to interact with.\n\n
        The museum is full of hands-on exhibits, making it perfect for families and visitors of all ages. There are sections dedicated to space exploration, transportation, and the human body. The museum is divided in sections, such as the Launchpad, who has many interactive exhibits.  \n\n
        Entry to the Science Museum is free, but there may be a charge for special exhibitions or the IMAX cinema. Check the museum\'s website for details on current exhibitions and any special events. You can also book online. \n\n
        Allow ample time to explore the many levels and exhibits.  Don\'t forget to take a photo with the iconic rockets and space crafts. Don\'t forget to ask!
    </string>

        <!-- 5. National Gallery -->
        <string name="national_gallery">The National Gallery</string>
        <string name="national_gallery_detail">
        The National Gallery, located in Trafalgar Square, houses one of the world\'s greatest collections of European paintings, spanning from the 13th to the 19th century.  It\'s a must-visit for art lovers, offering a comprehensive journey through art history. The gallery shows the evolution of painting. \n\n
        The collection includes works by masters such as Van Gogh, Leonardo da Vinci, Michelangelo, and Botticelli.  The paintings are displayed chronologically and by school, making it easy to follow the development of art. The National Gallery is divided into four areas. \n\n
        Entry to the National Gallery is free, but special exhibitions often require a paid ticket.  Be sure to check the gallery\'s website for current exhibition information. There are many tours available. There are also shops and restaurants.  \n\n
        Spend time getting up close to the masterpieces. Don\'t forget to admire the architecture of the building itself. Don\'t forget to ask!
    </string>

        <!-- 6. Tate Modern -->
        <string name="tate_modern">The Tate Modern</string>
        <string name="tate_modern_detail">
        The Tate Modern is Britain\'s national museum of international modern and contemporary art, housed in the former Bankside Power Station. Its iconic Turbine Hall is a must-see. The Tate Modern is a place of experimentation.\n\n
        The collection includes works by artists such as Picasso, Warhol, and Dalí. The museum\'s vast collection is displayed across multiple levels. The museum often hosts temporary exhibitions. The Tate Modern is one of the most interesting places. \n\n
        Entry to the Tate Modern is free, but special exhibitions may require a ticket. Be sure to check the museum\'s website for the latest exhibitions and events. The museum have many guided tours. \n\n
        Take the time to explore the building\'s architecture, as well as the art. Don\'t forget to admire the views of the city from the upper floors. Don\'t forget to ask!
    </string>

        <!-- 7. Churchill War Rooms -->
        <string name="churchill_war_rooms">The Churchill War Rooms</string>
        <string name="churchill_war_rooms_detail">
        The Churchill War Rooms offer a unique glimpse into life during World War II, housed in the underground bunker that served as the British government\'s headquarters during the Blitz. It is where Churchill and his government managed the Second World War.  This is one of the most interesting museum to visit.\n\n
        Explore the Cabinet War Rooms, where Churchill and his government strategized and planned during the war.  Visit the Churchill Museum to learn more about Churchill\'s life and leadership. The museum contains many historical artifacts.\n\n
        Entry to the Churchill War Rooms requires a paid ticket, and it\'s highly recommended to book in advance. This is a very popular attraction, so tickets often sell out. There is a gift shop and a cafe in the museum.\n\n
        Allow at least a couple of hours to fully explore the War Rooms. Don\'t forget to take the audio guide for a more immersive experience. Don\'t forget to ask!
    </string>

<!--    Category 3 - Transport-->
        <!-- 1. The Tube (Underground) -->
        <string name="tube">The London Underground: The Tube</string>
        <string name="tube_detail">
        The London Underground, affectionately known as the \'Tube,\' is the world\'s first underground railway and a vital part of London\'s transport system. With 11 lines and 272 stations, it efficiently connects most of the city and its suburbs. Each line is color-coded and named, making it relatively easy to navigate. The Tube is usually the fastest way to travel across central London, particularly during peak hours when road traffic can be heavy.  \n\n
        Understanding the Tube\'s zones is crucial for planning your journey and purchasing tickets. Zones 1 and 2 cover central London, while the outer zones extend to the suburbs.  Oyster cards and contactless payments are the most convenient ways to pay for your travel.  Make sure you tap in and tap out at the start and end of your journey. \n\n
        During rush hour, the Tube can get incredibly crowded, especially on popular lines. Be prepared to stand or squeeze into packed carriages during peak times.  Also, keep an eye out for service updates, as lines can occasionally be closed for maintenance or experience delays. Despite these challenges, the Tube remains an iconic and incredibly efficient way to explore London.\n\n
        Don\'t forget to download a Tube map app for easy navigation. Remember to mind the gap when entering or exiting the train! It\'s essential to listen for announcements and be aware of your surroundings. Don\'t forget to ask!
    </string>

        <!-- 2. Buses -->
        <string name="buses">London\'s Iconic Red Buses</string>
        <string name="buses_detail">
        London\'s red double-decker buses are an iconic symbol of the city and a fantastic way to see the sights. The bus network is extensive, covering nearly every part of London. There are multiple types of buses and some of them run 24-hours.\n\n
        Buses are generally slower than the Tube, especially during rush hour. However, they provide a more scenic travel experience, allowing you to see more of the city as you go. You can use the same Oyster card or contactless payment method as the Tube, but be sure to only tap in when you board, not when you exit. Buses can take you to various interesting locations, including museums and galleries.\n\n
        Night buses are a lifesaver for those out late. Most night buses are marked with the letter \'N\' before their route number, such as N29. Bus stops are marked with a red sign, and each stop has a list of the routes that pass through it. The bus will stop at every bus station unless the passenger press the stop button. \n\n
        Don\'t forget to download a bus map app to discover all routes! Remember to wave your hand when you see your bus approaching to make sure the driver sees you. Don\'t forget to ask!
    </string>

        <!-- 3. Docklands Light Railway (DLR) -->
        <string name="dlr">Docklands Light Railway (DLR)</string>
        <string name="dlr_detail">
        The Docklands Light Railway (DLR) is an automated light metro system that primarily serves the Docklands area of East London. It connects to the Underground network at several points, providing easy access to Canary Wharf, Greenwich, and London City Airport. The DLR is a great way to travel around the eastern part of the city, especially if you\'re visiting Canary Wharf or Greenwich.\n\n
        One of the unique features of the DLR is that it\'s driverless. This means you can often sit at the front of the train and enjoy the view as it travels through the city. The DLR also operates within the same fare zones as the Underground and buses, and Oyster and contactless payments are accepted.  Many of the stations are above ground, offering great views of the developing Docklands area.\n\n
        The DLR can get quite busy during the work week, as many people commute to Canary Wharf. The trains are frequent, however, so you usually won\'t have to wait long. While it\'s a convenient way to navigate the area, be sure to check service updates, especially on weekends, as there may be planned engineering works.\n\n
        Don\'t forget to plan your journey in advance, especially if you\'re travelling to London City Airport. Remember to tap in and out at the stations to get the correct fare. Don\'t forget to ask!
    </string>

        <!-- 4. Overground -->
        <string name="overground">London Overground</string>
        <string name="overground_detail">
        The London Overground is a suburban railway network that circles much of Greater London, providing connections between areas not directly served by the Underground.  With its distinctive orange roundel, the Overground offers a vital link between the city\'s various districts and suburbs. It is a convenient way to reach locations that are further from the center of London. \n\n
        The Overground connects to the Tube network at numerous stations, making it easy to transfer between the two systems. Oyster cards, contactless payments, and paper tickets are accepted on the Overground, similar to the Tube and buses. Most of the Overground is above ground, giving you an insight into the areas of London outside of the center.\n\n
        The Overground trains are generally less crowded than the Tube, especially outside of peak hours. Be aware that service frequencies can vary depending on the route and time of day.  It\'s always a good idea to check for any planned engineering works before you travel, especially on weekends.\n\n
        Don\'t forget to check the Overground map for useful connections to other transportation options. Remember that this system mainly goes above ground, so you can enjoy the views. Don\'t forget to ask!
    </string>

        <!-- 5. Trams -->
        <string name="trams">London\'s Tram Network</string>
        <string name="trams_detail">
        London\'s tram network, currently known as Tramlink, primarily serves the South London area, particularly around Croydon.  Trams are a smooth, comfortable, and often less crowded alternative to buses, offering a different way to get around in this part of the city. The trams run on dedicated tracks, so they are not affected by road traffic. \n\n
        Tramlink connects to the National Rail network at several stations, making it easy to transfer to other parts of London and beyond. The same Oyster cards and contactless payments used on the Tube and buses are valid on the trams. You only need to tap in when you board the tram, not when you exit. Trams are known for being particularly punctual and for having a smooth ride.\n\n
        The tram network is quite limited compared to the Tube or bus network, focusing primarily on South London. However, it\'s a very useful option if you\'re travelling within the areas it serves. The trams are quite modern and have large windows, so you get a great view of the area. \n\n
        Don\'t forget to check the tram route map if you\'re travelling in South London. Remember to look at the tram destination to ensure you\'re getting on the correct service. Don\'t forget to ask!
    </string>

        <!-- 6. National Rail -->
        <string name="national_rail">National Rail Services</string>
        <string name="national_rail_detail">
        National Rail services are the main intercity train lines that connect London to the rest of the UK.  London has numerous major train stations, each serving different parts of the country.  These stations include King\'s Cross, Paddington, Euston, Victoria, and Waterloo, among others. These stations are usually connected to the Tube and buses.\n\n
        National Rail services are an essential way to reach places outside of London, whether you\'re heading to a coastal town, a historic city, or the countryside.  Trains are generally much faster than buses for long-distance journeys, but ticket prices vary widely depending on the route and the time of travel. It\'s important to plan your journey ahead.\n\n
        You can often get discounted fares if you book your tickets in advance, especially for long-distance travel.  Make sure to check the departure platform and any potential delays before you travel. Train stations can be very busy, especially during rush hour, so give yourself plenty of time to navigate through them. There are usually many shops and restaurants in the train stations.\n\n
        Don\'t forget to check your train schedule and departure platform carefully. Remember to be aware of your belongings at all times, especially in busy stations. Don\'t forget to ask!
    </string>

        <!-- 7. River Bus (Thames Clippers) -->
        <string name="river_bus">River Bus (Thames Clippers)</string>
        <string name="river_bus_detail">
        The River Bus, also known as Thames Clippers, is a unique way to travel around London and offers a different perspective of the city from the River Thames.  The River Bus operates a network of piers between Putney and Wool
        </string>

    <!-- Category 4 - Sports Stadium-->

        <!-- 1. Arsenal Emirates Stadium -->
        <string name="arsenal_emirates_stadium">Arsenal Emirates Stadium</string>
        <string name="arsenal_emirates_stadium_subtitle">Home of the Gunners</string>
        <string name="arsenal_emirates_stadium_detail">
        The Emirates Stadium is the home of Arsenal Football Club, one of the most successful and popular football clubs in England. It\'s a modern, state-of-the-art stadium that provides an incredible experience for football fans.  It replaced Highbury, which was Arsenal\'s home for 93 years.\n\n
        Visitors can take a stadium tour to explore behind the scenes, including the dressing rooms, the players\' tunnel, and the Arsenal Museum. On match days, the atmosphere is electric, with passionate fans cheering on the Gunners. There are multiple restaurants and shops around the area.\n\n
        Tickets for matches and tours can be booked online in advance.  The stadium is easily accessible by public transport, with its own tube station.  Allow at least 2 to 3 hours to enjoy the museum and the tour. \n\n
        Don\'t forget to visit the Arsenal Museum to learn more about the club\'s rich history. Remember to wear red and white if you\'re attending a match! Don\'t forget to ask!
    </string>

        <!-- 2. Lord's Cricket Ground -->
        <string name="lords_cricket_ground">Lord\'s Cricket Ground</string>
        <string name="lords_cricket_ground_subtitle">The Home of Cricket</string>
        <string name="lords_cricket_ground_detail">
        Lord\'s Cricket Ground, often referred to as the "Home of Cricket," is one of the most famous and historic cricket grounds in the world.  It\'s a must-visit for any cricket enthusiast, and offers a unique glimpse into the history of this great sport. The first international match was held in 1884.\n\n
        Visitors can take a tour of the ground to see the famous Long Room, the MCC Museum, and the Real Tennis Court.  On match days, you can experience the excitement of Test matches, One Day Internationals, and other cricket events. You can also find restaurants and shops in the area.\n\n
        Tickets for matches and tours can be booked online in advance.  Lord\'s is easily accessible by public transport.  Allow at least 2 to 3 hours for a tour of the museum and the ground.  It also hosts other events, including conferences.\n\n
        Don\'t forget to visit the MCC Museum to see the Ashes Urn and other cricket memorabilia. Remember to take photos of this iconic venue. Don\'t forget to ask!
    </string>

        <!-- 3. The Oval -->
        <string name="the_oval">The Oval</string>
        <string name="the_oval_subtitle">Historic Cricket Venue</string>
        <string name="the_oval_detail">
        The Oval, officially known as the Kia Oval, is another of London\'s iconic cricket grounds.  It has a rich history and has hosted many memorable cricket matches, including the first-ever Test match in England. There are also many shops and restaurants in the area.\n\n
        Visitors can take a tour of the ground to learn about its history and explore behind-the-scenes areas.  On match days, you can experience the thrill of international and county cricket. It is located in the Kennington area.\n\n
        Tickets for matches and tours can be booked online in advance. The Oval is easily accessible by public transport, with its own tube station. Allow at least 2 hours to tour the ground and museum. \n\n
        Don\'t forget to check the schedule for upcoming matches and events. Remember to enjoy the atmosphere of this historic sporting venue. Don\'t forget to ask!
    </string>

        <!-- 4. Twickenham Stadium -->
        <string name="twickenham_stadium">Twickenham Stadium</string>
        <string name="twickenham_stadium_subtitle">Home of England Rugby</string>
        <string name="twickenham_stadium_detail">
        Twickenham Stadium is the home of England Rugby and one of the largest rugby stadiums in the world. It hosts numerous international matches, including Six Nations matches, and is known for its passionate and vibrant atmosphere on match days. You will find multiple shops and restaurants in the area.\n\n
        Visitors can take a stadium tour to explore the dressing rooms, the Royal Box, and the World Rugby Museum.  On match days, the stadium comes alive with thousands of fans cheering on the England team. It is the largest dedicated rugby union venue in the world.\n\n
        Tickets for matches and tours can be booked online in advance.  Twickenham is easily accessible by public transport.  Allow at least 2 to 3 hours to tour the stadium and the museum. \n\n
        Don\'t forget to visit the World Rugby Museum to learn about the history of the sport. Remember to sing "Swing Low, Sweet Chariot" if you\'re attending a match! Don\'t forget to ask!
    </string>

        <!-- 5. Wembley Stadium -->
        <string name="wembley_stadium">Wembley Stadium</string>
        <string name="wembley_stadium_subtitle">Iconic Football Venue</string>
        <string name="wembley_stadium_detail">
        Wembley Stadium is one of the most iconic football stadiums in the world, and it is the largest stadium in the UK. It is known as the "Home of Football." It hosts major football matches, including FA Cup finals, England international games, and UEFA Champions League finals. It also hosts many concerts.\n\n
        Visitors can take a stadium tour to explore the dressing rooms, the Royal Box, and the players\' tunnel.  On match days, the atmosphere is unforgettable, with passionate fans creating a spectacular scene. It has hosted numerous high-profile sports events.\n\n
        Tickets for matches and tours can be booked online in advance. Wembley is easily accessible by public transport, with its own tube station. Allow at least 2 hours to fully explore the stadium. There are also many shops and restaurants around the area.\n\n
        Don\'t forget to take photos of the stadium\'s iconic arch. Remember to join in the singing if you\'re at a match! Don\'t forget to ask!
    </string>

        <!-- 6. Tottenham Hotspur Stadium -->
        <string name="tottenham_hotspur_stadium">Tottenham Hotspur Stadium</string>
        <string name="tottenham_hotspur_stadium_subtitle">Home of the Spurs</string>
        <string name="tottenham_hotspur_stadium_detail">
        The Tottenham Hotspur Stadium is the new home of Tottenham Hotspur Football Club, and it is one of the most technologically advanced stadiums in the world.  It offers a unique and immersive experience for football fans. It is known for its retractable pitch.\n\n
        Visitors can take a stadium tour to explore the behind-the-scenes areas, including the dressing rooms and the players\' tunnel.  On match days, the atmosphere is electric, with passionate fans cheering on the Spurs. It also hosts many concerts and events.\n\n
        Tickets for matches and tours can be booked online in advance.  The stadium is easily accessible by public transport.  Allow at least 2 to 3 hours to enjoy the museum and the tour. There are also shops and restaurants.\n\n
        Don\'t forget to try some of the food and drink options available at the stadium. Remember to wear navy blue and white if you\'re attending a match! Don\'t forget to ask!
    </string>

    <!-- 26. Wimbledon -->
    <string name="wimbledon">Wimbledon</string>
    <string name="wimbledon_subtitle">The Championships</string>
    <string name="wimbledon_detail">
        Wimbledon is the oldest tennis tournament in the world and is considered the most prestigious. It is held at the All England Lawn Tennis and Croquet Club in Wimbledon, London. It is the only Grand Slam tournament still played on grass. It is one of the most important events in tennis.\n\n
        Visitors can take a tour of the grounds, including Centre Court and the Wimbledon Lawn Tennis Museum. During the tournament, you can witness some of the world\'s best tennis players competing for the coveted title. The area has many restaurants and shops.\n\n
        Tickets for the tournament are in high demand and are usually distributed through a public ballot.  Tours of the grounds are available throughout the year and can be booked in advance. Wimbledon is accessible by public transport, with its own tube station. Allow at least 2 to 3 hours to explore.\n\n
        Don\'t forget to try some strawberries and cream, a traditional Wimbledon treat. Remember to take photos of the beautiful grounds. Don\'t forget to ask!
    </string>

<!--    Category 5 - Theatre-->
        <!-- 1. The National Theatre -->
        <string name="the_national_theatre">The National Theatre</string>
        <string name="the_national_theatre_subtitle">South Bank Landmark</string>
        <string name="the_national_theatre_detail">
        The National Theatre is one of the United Kingdom\'s most prominent publicly funded performing arts venues.  Located on the South Bank of the River Thames, it\'s renowned for its diverse and high-quality productions, ranging from Shakespeare to contemporary plays. There are three theatres.\n\n
        Visitors can watch a wide range of performances, from classic plays to new works.  The theatre also offers backstage tours, giving you a behind-the-scenes glimpse into the world of theatre. There are multiple restaurants and shops around the theatre.\n\n
        Tickets for performances and tours can be booked online in advance. The National Theatre is easily accessible by public transport.  Allow at least 2 to 3 hours to explore the building and attend a performance. This is a famous and beautiful place.\n\n
        Don\'t forget to take a stroll along the South Bank before or after your visit. Remember to check the theatre\'s website for the current schedule. Don\'t forget to ask!
    </string>

        <!-- 2. Shakespeare's Globe -->
        <string name="shakespeares_globe">Shakespeare\'s Globe</string>
        <string name="shakespeares_globe_subtitle">The Bard\'s Theatre</string>
        <string name="shakespeares_globe_detail">
        Shakespeare\'s Globe is a reconstruction of the original Elizabethan playhouse where many of Shakespeare\'s plays were first performed.  It offers a unique theatrical experience, celebrating the work of England\'s greatest playwright. You will find shops and restaurants nearby.\n\n
        Visitors can attend performances in the open-air theatre, often in a traditional Elizabethan style. You can also take a tour of the Globe and learn about the history of Shakespeare and the original theatre. It is located by the River Thames.\n\n
        Tickets for performances and tours can be booked online in advance. The Globe is easily accessible by public transport. Allow at least 2 to 3 hours to tour the theatre and attend a performance. You will have a great experience.\n\n
        Don\'t forget to check the schedule for any special events or workshops. Remember to experience a play in the atmospheric surroundings. Don\'t forget to ask!
    </string>

        <!-- 3. Royal Opera House -->
        <string name="royal_opera_house">Royal Opera House</string>
        <string name="royal_opera_house_subtitle">Opera and Ballet Venue</string>
        <string name="royal_opera_house_detail">
        The Royal Opera House is one of the world\'s leading opera and ballet venues, located in Covent Garden. It\'s home to The Royal Opera and The Royal Ballet, and it hosts a wide range of world-class performances throughout the year. This is one of the most beautiful places.\n\n
        Visitors can attend performances of opera and ballet, often featuring some of the world\'s greatest performers.  The Royal Opera House also offers tours, giving you a chance to explore behind the scenes. You will find shops and restaurants in the area.\n\n
        Tickets for performances and tours can be booked online in advance.  The Royal Opera House is easily accessible by public transport. Allow at least 2 to 3 hours to enjoy a performance or take a tour. \n\n
        Don\'t forget to dress up for a special evening at the opera or ballet. Remember to check the website for the latest performance schedule. Don\'t forget to ask!
    </string>

        <!-- 4. Theatre Royal Drury Lane -->
        <string name="theatre_royal_drury_lane">Theatre Royal Drury Lane</string>
        <string name="theatre_royal_drury_lane_subtitle">Historic West End Theatre</string>
        <string name="theatre_royal_drury_lane_detail">
        The Theatre Royal Drury Lane is one of London\'s oldest and most historic theatres, located in the heart of the West End.  It has hosted a wide range of performances over the centuries, from plays and musicals to opera and ballet. It is also known as the Lane.\n\n
        Visitors can attend performances of popular musicals and plays, often featuring top West End talent.  The theatre also offers guided tours, allowing you to learn about its rich history. The theatre is surrounded by shops and restaurants. \n\n
        Tickets for performances and tours can be booked online in advance. The theatre is easily accessible by public transport.  Allow at least 2 to 3 hours to enjoy a performance or tour. \n\n
        Don\'t forget to check the schedule for any special events or productions. Remember to admire the theatre\'s beautiful interior. Don\'t forget to ask!
    </string>

        <!-- 5. London Palladium -->
        <string name="london_palladium">London Palladium</string>
        <string name="london_palladium_subtitle">Variety and Musical Theatre</string>
        <string name="london_palladium_detail">
        The London Palladium is one of the most famous theatres in the West End, known for its variety of shows, musicals, and concerts.  It has hosted some of the biggest names in show business over the years and continues to be a popular venue. \n\n
        Visitors can attend performances of musicals, plays, concerts, and variety shows, often featuring well-known performers.  The theatre\'s interior is a beautiful example of Edwardian architecture. You will find many restaurants and shops around.\n\n
        Tickets for performances can be booked online in advance. The London Palladium is easily accessible by public transport. Allow at least 2 to 3 hours to enjoy a performance. This is a great place to go.\n\n
        Don\'t forget to check the schedule for upcoming shows and concerts. Remember to take in the atmosphere of this historic venue. Don\'t forget to ask!
    </string>

        <!-- 6. Old Vic Theatre -->
        <string name="old_vic_theatre">Old Vic Theatre</string>
        <string name="old_vic_theatre_subtitle">Iconic London Theatre</string>
        <string name="old_vic_theatre_detail">
        The Old Vic Theatre is a historic theatre located in Waterloo, known for its innovative and often experimental productions. It has been a hub of theatrical creativity for over 200 years. It has hosted some of the biggest names in theatre.\n\n
        Visitors can attend performances of a wide range of plays, often featuring well-known actors and directors.  The theatre also offers workshops and events. The area is surrounded by shops and restaurants. \n\n
        Tickets for performances can be booked online in advance. The Old Vic is easily accessible by public transport.  Allow at least 2 to 3 hours to enjoy a performance. This is a beautiful theatre. \n\n
        Don\'t forget to explore the Waterloo area before or after your visit. Remember to check the theatre\'s website for upcoming productions. Don\'t forget to ask!
    </string>

        <!-- 7. The Apollo Theatre -->
        <string name="the_apollo_theatre">The Apollo Theatre</string>
        <string name="the_apollo_theatre_subtitle">West End Classic</string>
        <string name="the_apollo_theatre_detail">
        The Apollo Theatre is a beautiful, Grade II listed West End theatre, known for hosting a wide variety of shows, musicals, and plays. It is one of the most beautiful theatre in London. It has been a popular destination for theatregoers for over a century.\n\n
        Visitors can attend a wide range of performances, from musicals and plays to concerts and comedy shows.  The theatre\'s elegant interior is a treat in itself.  The surrounding area offers a multitude of dining and shopping options.\n\n
        Tickets for performances can be booked online in advance. The Apollo Theatre is easily accessible by public transport.  Allow at least 2 to 3 hours to enjoy a performance. \n\n
        Don\'t forget to take in the beautiful details of the theatre\'s design. Remember to check the theatre\'s website for their latest schedule. Don\'t forget to ask!
    </string>

<!--    Category - 6 Shopping in London-->

        <!-- 34. Oxford Street -->
        <string name="oxford_street">Oxford Street</string>
        <string name="oxford_street_subtitle">London\'s Shopping Heart</string>
        <string name="oxford_street_detail">
        Oxford Street is one of London\'s most famous and busiest shopping streets, home to over 300 shops, from major department stores to high-street fashion brands and international retailers. It\'s a must-visit destination for any shopping enthusiast. It is very popular during the Christmas period. \n\n
        Visitors can find everything from clothing and accessories to electronics, homeware, and souvenirs. The street is also home to flagship stores of many popular brands. There are multiple restaurants around the area. \n\n
        Oxford Street is easily accessible by public transport, with several tube stations along the street.  Be prepared for large crowds, especially during peak times.  Allow at least a few hours to explore the various shops. It is a great place to go.\n\n
        Don\'t forget to check out the side streets for smaller boutiques and unique finds. Remember to visit during the week if you want to avoid the busiest crowds. Don\'t forget to ask!
    </string>

        <!-- 35. Covent Garden -->
        <string name="covent_garden">Covent Garden</string>
        <string name="covent_garden_subtitle">Shopping, Culture, and Entertainment</string>
        <string name="covent_garden_detail">
        Covent Garden is a vibrant area in London that combines shopping, culture, and entertainment.  It\'s known for its historic market building, street performers, and diverse range of shops, from high-end brands to unique boutiques.  It\'s a great place to spend an afternoon or evening. \n\n
        Visitors can explore the Apple Market, which features handmade crafts, art, and unique gifts.  The surrounding streets are home to a variety of shops, restaurants, and theatres. There is also the famous Royal Opera House. \n\n
        Covent Garden is easily accessible by public transport. Be sure to check out the street performers in the Piazza. Allow a few hours to explore the area. There is a great atmosphere. \n\n
        Don\'t forget to browse the independent shops for unique items. Remember to take in the lively atmosphere and watch the street performers. Don\'t forget to ask!
    </string>

        <!-- 36. Regent Street -->
        <string name="regent_street">Regent Street</string>
        <string name="regent_street_subtitle">Elegant Shopping and Architecture</string>
        <string name="regent_street_detail">
        Regent Street is known for its elegant architecture and high-end shops, including iconic toy store Hamleys and the historic Liberty London department store.  It\'s a beautiful street to stroll down, even if you\'re not planning on shopping. The architecture is amazing.\n\n
        Visitors can find a wide range of luxury brands, department stores, and flagship stores.  The street is also known for its beautiful Christmas lights during the holiday season. There are restaurants in the area. \n\n
        Regent Street is easily accessible by public transport. Allow at least a few hours to explore the various shops and take in the atmosphere. It is a beautiful place to visit. \n\n
        Don\'t forget to take photos of the street\'s stunning architecture. Remember to explore the side streets for more unique shops and boutiques. Don\'t forget to ask!
    </string>

        <!-- 37. Bond Street -->
        <string name="bond_street">Bond Street</string>
        <string name="bond_street_subtitle">Luxury Shopping in Mayfair</string>
        <string name="bond_street_detail">
        Bond Street, located in the affluent Mayfair district, is synonymous with luxury shopping.  It\'s home to some of the world\'s most exclusive fashion brands, jewelry stores, and art galleries.  It\'s a destination for those looking for high-end goods and designer labels. \n\n
        Visitors can find designer clothing, luxury watches, fine jewelry, and high-end art.  The street is also lined with elegant buildings and exclusive restaurants. It is close to the Royal Academy of Arts.\n\n
        Bond Street is easily accessible by public transport. Allow a few hours to explore the various shops and galleries.  It is a very luxurious area.\n\n
        Don\'t forget to window-shop, even if you\'re not planning on making a purchase. Remember to take in the atmosphere of this luxurious area. Don\'t forget to ask!
    </string>

        <!-- 38. Carnaby Street -->
        <string name="carnaby_street">Carnaby Street</string>
        <string name="carnaby_street_subtitle">Independent and Boutique Shopping</string>
        <string name="carnaby_street_detail">
        Carnaby Street is a vibrant and pedestrianized shopping area in Soho, known for its independent boutiques, fashion brands, and unique atmosphere.  It\'s a great place to find something different from the mainstream, with a strong emphasis on fashion and lifestyle. \n\n
        Visitors can explore a wide range of independent shops, fashion boutiques, and lifestyle stores.  The area is also home to numerous restaurants, bars, and cafes. It is one of the best areas to shop. \n\n
        Carnaby Street is easily accessible by public transport. Allow at least a few hours to explore the various shops and soak up the atmosphere.  It is very vibrant.\n\n
        Don\'t forget to check out the side streets and courtyards for more hidden gems. Remember to browse the independent boutiques for unique items. Don\'t forget to ask!
    </string>

        <!-- 39. Westfield London -->
        <string name="westfield_london">Westfield London</string>
        <string name="westfield_london_subtitle">Modern Shopping Mall</string>
        <string name="westfield_london_detail">
        Westfield London is one of the largest urban shopping centres in Europe, offering a vast range of shops, restaurants, and entertainment options. It\'s a modern and convenient shopping destination, with something for everyone. It is located in White City.\n\n
        Visitors can find major department stores, high-street fashion brands, luxury retailers, and a wide range of restaurants and cafes.  The mall also has a cinema and other entertainment facilities.  It is easily accessible by public transport. \n\n
        Westfield London is easily accessible by public transport.  You can easily spend a whole day exploring the mall. It has one of the best choice of shops.\n\n
        Don\'t forget to check the mall\'s website for any special events or promotions. Remember to wear comfortable shoes, as you\'ll be doing a lot of walking. Don\'t forget to ask!
    </string>

        <!-- 40. Harrods -->
        <string name="harrods">Harrods</string>
        <string name="harrods_subtitle">Luxury Department Store</string>
        <string name="harrods_detail">
        Harrods is one of the world\'s most famous department stores, known for its luxury goods, iconic food halls, and opulent interior.  It\'s a London landmark and a must-visit for those interested in high-end shopping and a unique retail experience. It is located in Knightsbridge.\n\n
        Visitors can explore a vast range of departments, from fashion and accessories to homeware, food, and beauty.  The Food Halls are particularly famous and are a destination in themselves. It is one of the most beautiful places.\n\n
        Harrods is easily accessible by public transport.  Allow at least a few hours to explore the various departments and food halls. It has an amazing atmosphere. \n\n
        Don\'t forget to visit the Food Halls, even if you\'re not planning on buying anything. Remember to take in the grand and opulent atmosphere of the store. Don\'t forget to ask!
    </string>




</resources>
