<resources>
    <string name="app_name">LondonMyCity</string>
     <!-- Strings used for fragments for navigation -->
    <string name="list_fragment_label">Sport</string>
    <string name="detail_fragment_label">Sport Info</string>

    <string name="attractions">Attractions</string>
    <string name="transport">Transport</string>
    <string name="museum">Museum</string>
    <string name="sport_stadium">Sports Stadium</string>
    <string name="theatre">Theatre</string>

    <!-- Category 1 for London City / London Attractions -->
    <string name="attraction_warnerbros_studio">Warner Bros. Studio Tour London</string>
    <string name="attraction_warnerbros_studio_detail">
      Have a magical day out with a behind-the-scenes tour of the Harry Potter films at Warner Bros.
      Studio Tour London The Making of Harry Potter. See first-hand the sets, costumes and props used in all the Harry Potter films, and step inside some of the films locations, including the Great Hall, Dumbledore\'s office and Hagrid\'s hut.
      It\'s the ultimate Harry Potter experience!
    </string>
    <string name="attraction_the_london_eye">The London Eye</string>
    <string name="attraction_the_london_eye_detail">
     Climb aboard one of the 32 glass capsules of the London Eye for unforgettable views of some of London\'s most famous landmarks. Take in amazing 360-degree views as the capsule slowly rotates over the river Thames.
    </string>
    <string name="attraction_hopon_hopoff">Hop-on hop-off bus tour</string>
    <string name="attraction_hopon_hopoff_detail">
      Make the most of your trip to London with a hop-on hop-off bus tour.
      Spot iconic sites with a live guide (or audio guide) and hop on and off the sightseeing buses as often as you like.
      Famous attractions you\'ll see en route include Buckingham Palace, the London Eye and St Paul\'s Cathedral.
    </string>
    <string name="attraction_tower_of_london">Tower of London</string>
    <string name="attraction_tower_of_london_detail">
     Take a tour with one of the Yeoman Warders around the Tower of London, one of the world\'s most famous buildings.
     Discover its 900-year history as a royal palace, prison and place of execution, arsenal, jewel house and zoo! Gaze up at the White Tower, tiptoe through a medieval king\'s bedchamber and marvel at the Crown Jewels.
    </string>
    <string name="attraction_buckingham_palace">Buckingham Palace</string>
    <string name="attraction_buckingham_palace_detail">
     Enjoy a glimpse into the life of royalty with a visit to this iconic London palace for a limited time each summer. 
     Wander through the grand State Rooms, discovering many treasures and artefacts, and marvel at a special exhibition. 
     Finish your self-guided tour in the quaint gardens, where you can see the famous lake.
    </string>
    <string name="attraction_madame_tussauds">Madame Tussauds London</string>
    <string name="attraction_madame_tussauds_detail">
     At Madame Tussauds London, you\'ll come face-to-face with some of the world\'s most famous faces. From Shakespeare to Taylor Swift, you\'ll meet influential figures from showbiz, sport, politics and even royalty.
     Strike a pose with Usain Bolt, get close to Beyonc\é or enjoy the Marvel Universe 4D Experience.
    </string>
    <string name="attraction_british_museum">British Museum</string>
    <string name="attraction_british_museum_detail">
      See the best of the world\’s history, art and culture on a two-hour British Museum Guided Tour. 
      Led by an expert guide, highlights include the world-famous Rosetta Stone, the key to deciphering Egyptian hieroglyphics, relics from The Sutton Hoo ship burial and more.
    </string>

    <!-- Category 2 for London City / Transport for London -->
    <string name="attraction_warnerbros_studio">Warner Bros. Studio Tour London</string>
    <string name="attraction_warnerbros_studio_detail">
      Have a magical day out with a behind-the-scenes tour of the Harry Potter films at Warner Bros.
      Studio Tour London The Making of Harry Potter. See first-hand the sets, costumes and props used in all the Harry Potter films, and step inside some of the films locations, including the Great Hall, Dumbledore\'s office and Hagrid\'s hut.
      It\'s the ultimate Harry Potter experience!
    </string>

     <string name="back_button">Back</string>
</resources>
